[Music: ‘He’s a Black Flame Dragon’ theme song]
[Exciting music]
Crazy...
[sigh]
[bird chirping]
[lively music]
(Sujeong) Why on earth did you kiss me?
No matter how drunk you are
Even if I think about it a hundred times
There is only one reason
(Juyeon) It’s too late today too
I don’t think I can leave it to dry.
Just keep your clothes.
Yes, why?
I don't really need it
Because she was pretty
Who will give me chocolate milk?
Now I only have Baek Soo-jeong.
[Emphasized sound effect]
(Edited) B
I like it
No, if you like it, you say you like it.
[laughter]
People are embarrassed
What if I start with a kiss?
How will you see my face from now on?
Ah, since when did I like you?
No way
From the beginning?
[chicken crowing]
[sigh]
[groans with difficulty]
Mr...
It's been all night, Mr...
[sigh]
[bird chirping]
[yawn]
[Embarrassed sigh]
[lively music]
(Edit) That...
Did you wake up early?
I didn't sleep well.
[Sujeong’s surprised gasp]
You said you couldn’t sleep?
yes
I guess
(Sujeong) I guess I was so nervous that I couldn’t sleep.
Would you have been able to sleep after doing something like that?
I guess I tend to hide my bed.
(Edit) I liked the obvious excuse.
Oh, I see.
Soo-jeong Baek, you really woke up early.
Didn't you sleep well?
Me?
Uh, no, I slept really well.
Well, I’m naturally an early morning person.
Miracle Morning, this is such a newbie style.
[Awkward laughter]
newborn style
(Juyeon) Could it be...
[Exciting music]
If you want to go for a walk, would you like to go with me?
Where?
There's a good place over there
(Edited) Why a good place...
[Surprise] Confession?
Are you confessing right away like this?
Oh, what should I answer?
If you refuse, when you do the job you said you refused.
It's not going to make you uncomfortable, right?
Ah, why do you like me?
It's causing trouble for people.
- Hey...
- I'll think about it first.
(Juyeon) Yes?
[Humorous music]
Yes?
(Juyeon) It's over there.
(Edit) Oh, what should I do?
I guess he even went on a preliminary field trip to confess.
Aren’t you going?
Go, go
[bird chirping]
[lively music]
[Sound effect of knocking on wooden table]
[Interesting music]
(Edited) Are you going to confess in a place like this?
Good place here...
yes
This is CEO Ahn yesterday
This is the mineral spring I mentioned.
(Juyeon) It tastes good too
[Juyeon’s powerful moans]
They say it’s good for hangovers too.
[bird chirping]
It's definitely delicious
Are you here to drink mineral water?
Then why do you come to the mineral spring?
[ding sound effect]
[Interesting Music - Continued]
yes
Because we’re not in a hurry to talk to each other.
(Juyeon) Baek Soo-jeong, try drinking it too.
I came this far
(Edited) You have to drink it.
Should we be salty among comrades?
[Sound of flowing water]
As expected
Cool and sweet, right?
yes
I feel so refreshed
[Sound of water being thrown away]
Then would you like some more?
No, I can do it.
[rattling sound]
[Sujeong's faint moan]
[The bowl falls]
[Exciting music]
[bird chirping]
[Sound of flowing water]
(Main lead) That...
So
Yes?
[Humorous sound effects]
(Juyeon) I can’t do it.
Here, here, intrusively
The leaves are falling
[humorous music]
I can't do it
Yongseong’s successor is
The place you stay should also be beautiful.
Let's go now
(Edited) No...
What is it?
Is this the bathroom or what?
(Sujeong) CEO, you really thought it through well.
He said he was thinking about it.
How did you decide exactly?
Thank you for returning my heart
As I said, I will guarantee you profits.
We will also pay utmost attention to customer convenience.
(Representative Ahn) Well, that’s enough, that’s enough
Talk to the employees at the dojo.
And I'll take a picture later
A
Of course the employees
I will trust and follow the CEO’s choice.
On behalf of Yongseong Department Store
(Juyeon) Don’t regret that choice
I'll do it for you [Interesting music]
[Sujeong’s awkward laughter]
Oh, is this what he is like?
(Edited) He was a scholarship student.
I want you to be very loyal to me.
Hey, if anyone sees it, they’ll think you’re the CEO.
[Laughing] He’s very picky.
Baek Soo-jeong
- This is for my sister!
- (Representative Ahn) Oh, no.
That's enough, that's done, that's done
Well, if you're Chairman Yongseong's grandson, huh?
It's no different from a representative.
[bright music]
(Juyeon) The CEO’s personality is such that he doesn’t order people around.
I think you are going directly
- I remembered
- (Representative Ahn) Huh?
(Juyeon) To my grandson
I know you want to be honest, but
Please take care of your subordinates as well.
You are older too.
Then my waist goes out.
[light laughter]
I have a habit of speaking
That's a lot of praise
No, they say they will do something like this
Do you think I'll be so moved that I'll sign a contract?
(Juyeon) Is that possible?
Because I’m not that naive.
(CEO Ahn) Huh?
Why would I have hidden it until the end?
Are you going to reveal it now?
To do business together
Because there has to be trust.
I'm sorry for not telling you from the beginning.
I wish you would have listened to us that much.
(Main role) Yongseong Chairman Jeong Hyo-seon
More than yourself
He is a person who cares about the company.
He is a person who can do anything for Yongseong.
In order for a company to do well
Society needs to do well too
You understand very well.
As a former grandson
I'm following my grandmother's wishes.
[light laughter]
If you contract with us, it will be through the foundation.
Strong Ranch is in progress
Hospital Donation Project Department
Ice cream factory equipment for patients
Let's invest
Is that serious?
yes
Those children will someday be like grandchildren.
Even the desire to be healthy
It's all sincere
[Bright Music - Continued]
(Edited) The head of the department said that?
(CEO Ahn) Yes, just as Team Leader Baek said.
Other guys will earn it
What I earn and spend
I thought it wouldn't get better
If you're willing to do that much
I'm fine, what are you doing?
(Sujeong) [Laughing] That’s right.
(Juyeon) Then let’s go.
(CEO Ahn) Yes
Oh, I have to take this.
This is our product
This is bellflower greens
I packed the seasoned godeulbaeki.
I hope you all ate well yesterday, huh?
(Edited) Ah...
- Take it.
- Me?
(CEO Ahn) Well, I heard they both eat well.
Take it, take it, this too, right
[Sujeong’s awkward laughter]
[Sujeong’s proud sigh]
(Sujeong) It’s rewarding to have come this far.
That's what you suggested to CEO Ahn.
Since when did you start thinking like that?
Baek Soo-jeong
It made me think like that.
[Exciting music]
Because you brought me here
[Car starting sound]
Yesterday...
Yes?
So yesterday
(Edited) Yesterday
What should I do?
Are you really going to say anything now?
[Sound of window rolling down]
(Juyeon) Is it hot? I turned on the air conditioner
[Sujeong’s embarrassed groan]
(Edited) No, it’s okay.
[light cough]
I'm ready, so tell me
What to prepare?
(Juyeon) Ah...
yesterday
I heard you had a hard time
[Interesting music]
Is that the end?
And if it's okay
If it's okay?
If it's okay, the song I listen to
Would you like to listen together?
yes
Please do so
(Juyeon) Play the song I used to listen to
(Voice) Crackshot's 'Follow me'
I'll let you know
[Loud rock music plays]
♪ Surrender yourself ♪
(Edited) Ah, what about the story?
When are you going to do it?
[sigh]
♪ Follow, follow, follow, follow me ♪
[Sound of car door opening and closing]
Then go in
Manager, it’s really like this.
Are you just going to go?
ah!
I forgot something important
[rustling sound]
[Cow crying]
[Juyeon’s groans of effort]
[light music]
Okay?
See you on Monday
Ah, what happens?
It happened last night, just...
Are you just going to move on like this?
Explain or do something
Shouldn't you do it?
It's already gone
Do I even need to explain?
Let's just overlook that kind of mistake.
- Mistake?
- Yes
A one-night stand caused by drunkenness.
(Main lead) Isn’t it for Baek Soo-jeong?
[laughter]
That's right
(Edit) Mistake
[Sujeong’s light sigh]
It's a mistake and an accident.
Did you think I was crazy?
As you know, former head of the department
I never see you as a man.
[Heavy sound effect]
[absurd gasping sound]
[Interesting music]
(Juyeon) Why do you suddenly say that?
Did anyone even beg to be seen as a man?
It would have been better if I had asked for it.
[Sighing] Sheesh
What is it?
He looks like a man
(Edited) Crazy
Can you just overlook a mistake like that?
When I'm drunk, I kiss you
You're not a flirt!
[sigh]
Why on earth are you so mad?
[humorous music]
[Juyeon’s labored groans]
(Main role) Makgeolli
It's not right either
You fell asleep while waiting for me to call you.
[light music]
But leave me alone
If I were to ask,
Aren't I the one who should be angry?
[laughter]
What is it
[Thumping sound]
Ah, Sujeong-ah
(Wonseop) Sujeong?
Uh, Dad
Did you call me?
What are you doing without even eating?
[Awkward laughter]
Because the door is strange
Even though I don't use it well
just
[eerie music]
I'm a little angry
[Creepy sound effect]
Because you can't break a person's head
Why?
Is it noisy? Should I not do it?
No, no, no, do it.
Uh, I have to, uh
My daughter does whatever she wants, eh.
(Edited) Yes
[Sujeong’s light smile]
[Hammering sound]
[Sujeong’s refreshing sigh]
[sigh]
yes
[humorous music]
Me too
drunk
Intoxicated by the atmosphere, that key...
Is that a big deal?
Is it something like a mistake overnight?
uh
[absurd elasticity]
mistake
[Filthy scream sound effect]
(Edited) If you still made a mistake
Shouldn't you apologize? [Filthy scream sound effect]
[Filthy scream sound effect]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[light sigh]
[tired sigh]
- (Main lead) Yes
- (Edited) Are you sleepy now?
(Main lead) Baek Soo-jeong?
[light sigh]
What's going on at the company?
The job is for both of us.
[Exciting music]
No matter how much I think about it, it’s ridiculous.
Yesterday, no, the day before yesterday
It's just a one night mistake
Is it the end if I say that?
So what do you say?
I was the one who was considerate, but why on earth?
I don't know if Baek Soo-jeong is angry.
That's consideration?
(Juyeon) Yes
Baek Soo-jeong accidentally gave me makgeolli.
I ended up spending a night at the ranch.
That's just a mistake
You're saying you'll let it go.
Considerate, very considerate.
[Sighing] That's not what we're talking about now.
(Juyeon) Oh, so that’s what you’re talking about?
Are you like this because you’re sorry?
[Drumming sound effect]
If you're sorry, just apologize
Why are you so angry for no reason?
Anyway
now
You want me to apologize?
[Exciting music]
Then do I do it?
While drinking together and talking
The person who disappeared should do it
(Juyeon) No, how can you wait?
Do you go in alone, leaving someone asleep?
No, I was shocked when I opened my eyes.
[Filthy scream sound effect]
It's cold and my back hurts
It was just a bug, it wasn't even a word.
That's why you couldn't sleep well.
That's it
This too, by being considerate.
I'll just move on.
Or did something else happen?
There wasn't
[Call end sound]
[Heavy sigh]
[upbeat music]
Remember...
I couldn't do it
[Sujeong shouts]
(Edited) Ah, what about men?
I heard you’re the same age as Soobin Baek.
Will I look like a man?
[absurd gasping sound]
Come to think of it, it was like that back then too.
Because treating me like my younger brother all day wasn’t enough
[Bewildered] Why me?
[Tiger growling sound effect]
Why don't I look like a man?
[sigh]
[Tiger growling sound effect]
[Exciting music]
[Heavy sigh]
(Trainer) 1 million twenty-one
Doesn't look like a man
(Trainer) 1 million twenty-two
as a man
- (Trainer) 1 million twenty-three
- (Main lead) I see it
as a man
[Heavy sigh]
(Juyeon) I didn't see it...
[groans with difficulty]
(Trainer) After 3 years
You've finally reached one million!
Thank you for your hard work
(Main Cast) One Million Twenty-Four Overview
- (Trainer) Ah...
- Let's count again from the beginning.
Next goal is 2 years
2 years
[Trainer sighs]
(Juyeon) Doesn’t look like a man
[Exciting music - continued]
[Heavy sigh]
- (Trainer) One
- (Main lead) Looks like a man
[Sound of water in shower]
Why don't I look like a man?
From the definition of looking like a man
Do I really need to know this?
[Sound effect popping]
(Juyeon) Director Kwon?
You and your husband met at your previous job, right?
One year younger
Well, what about it?
The moment I felt like a man
When was it?
[Interesting music]
[Embarrassed] Well, just...
Do your job well
It's already perfect
Spend my money well
it's so easy
(Juyeon) Is that all?
For being so considerate
Yeah, well that was the biggest one.
[laughter]
I already did that too
[light laughter]
(In-kyung) But it’s sudden.
a personal question for me
You never did it
Anything happens on the weekend
Were you there?
[humorous music]
It was an official question
I also know Director Kwon well.
Because it's my job
(Juyeon) Anyway, whatever
I liked that.
It's simple
[Rhythmic music]
(In-kyung) Do your job well
Spend my money well
For being so considerate
Yeah, well that was the biggest one.
Let’s all check our appearance together.
(Voice) Check your appearance!
(Juyeon) It’s too good to be used only as a resting space
It's a bit of a waste.
If you do well, you will get new customers.
To lure you to a department store
Couldn’t it play a bigger role?
(Hyeju) That’s right
Now that I see it, I can’t just leave it alone.
It's a bit of a waste of space.
(Team Leader) As expected, the head of the division.
You have extraordinary eyes
[laughter]
What do you think of Team Leader Baek Soo-jeong?
sounds like a good idea
Let's find a way to use it
good
It’s still before lunch, right?
yes?
(Edited) Yes, yes
Then let’s go to the Yongseong Hotel next door.
[Sound effect of pointing]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Exciting music]
to existing work
A renewal project has also been added
(Juyeon) I know you’ve been through a lot.
In that sense
I'll treat you to lunch today.
Here!
The pride of Yongseong Hotel
At The S-Class Buffet
[Employees’ happy exclamations and applause]
(Employee 1) Thank you
(Juyeon) Let’s eat as much as we want
(Employees) Thank you
- (Employee 2) Thank you
- (Employee 3) Thank you
(Juyeon) One lobster per person
I prepared it for you to eat.
[Sound effect of pointing]
[Humorous sound effects]
[light laughter]
[Elegant music plays]
[Employee 4’s exclamation]
(Employee 5) How much is this? Just shoot?
Even if I can't do it, I think it'll be 20 per person.
(Employee 4) There is a rumor that he is the chairman’s grandson.
I guess it's real
Ah, the Yongseong Hotel chefs.
Write like your own personal chef
(Employee 5) Oh, but
Are you working hard at work?
[Overwhelming elasticity]
I really want to get involved so badly
[Employee 4’s exclamation]
(Employee 4) Then the design team
He must be more popular than Director Kim.
(Employee 5) So
(Hyeju) I thought Director Ban was being harsh.
You have all this sense?
I don't date because I'm a workaholic.
It seemed like all I did was work.
The woman who catches the head of the class
It's a complete catch, isn't it?
Suddenly he said that to me
Why are you doing this?
(Hyeju) Surprisingly, the two get along well.
They seem to get along well
Our Team Leader Baek
Maybe they're aiming for a rise in social status?
I thought you weren't that type
Of course it's not that style, right?
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
(Edited) The head of the department
Because he's just my boss.
What about dating or marriage?
I've never thought about it
(Juyeon) Then, why not think about it?
[Interesting music]
My name is the head of the planning team.
I feel like I lack creativity.
[Junsu and Nana talking]
(Nana) Enjoy your meal
- Enjoy your meal
- (Junsu) Enjoy your meal
[Junsu clears his throat]
(Seokhee) Enjoy your meal, Director.
Lack of creativity?
Don't worry about your memory
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Throws away the tissue]
Uh, sister
(Hajin) Is it okay to talk?
Nothing much happened over the weekend, right?
Any big deal?
Coming home with the manager
I guess nothing much happened until that moment
There wasn't
With that bully idiot
what's going on
At some point they said I seemed like a good person again
Are we back to square one again?
Also added is an idiot.
What, is that why you called?
No, do you want to go on a blind date?
[light music]
It's because there's someone who really seems like a good fit for you.
First of all, he is older and a lawyer by profession.
(Hajin) Very understanding
Reliable and friendly personality
He's just your ideal type
child
Don't say we won't meet again
Think about it for a moment
[Swooshing sound effect]
[Grabbing sound effect]
(Ha Jin-mo) Hey!
[Hajin’s surprised exclamation]
Oh, oh, oh, you burnt-out!
[Hajin’s pained moans]
you do it you
Oh, really, oh, oh, oh
- Wow, you really...
- (Hajin) Boy, it’s really true.
It hurts!
I really don't need it
(Hajin Mo) Oh, like that
Because there is no sharpness
As soon as you get married, you start living simple lives.
[The sound of Hajin giving medicine]
You are the same
Where are the two of us just like, oh, really
What kind of blind date is it?
(Junsu) Team leader
[Closes cell phone]
Are you on a blind date?
[humorous music]
Well thought out, team leader.
How old are you? What is your job?
Wait a minute, I need to meet that team leader.
It wouldn't work for most jobs.
They say you’re handsome?
Of course, you should also look at the height, right?
How tall are you?
These days, I took off my shoes
You need to check
That hasn't been decided yet
Well, I'm not sure...
(Juyeon) Who is going on a blind date?
(Junsu) Ah, team leader.
Is it real?
I asked if it was real
Why are you curious about that?
Uh, uh, don't worry, manager.
(Junsu) The team leader said he was just dating.
not working hard
You wouldn't do that, would you?
(In-kyung) Director
The Chairman is looking for you
Team leader Baek
(Juyeon) Come see me for a moment before you get off work.
(Junsu) You seemed in a good mood earlier.
Why is it like that?
(In-kyung) Congratulations
Manager's lifelong wish
It won't be long before it comes true
The head of the department was fully exposed to the media.
Weren't there instructions to expose it?
position as successor
You probably want to make it official.
Until the success of this renewal project
I thought you would be watching
It's faster than I thought
If it stays like this, there will be no problem
It seems like you are preparing in advance.
(In-kyung) Actually
When I was reporting earlier, the chairman said
You asked about the general manager.
What was it like watching closely?
I don't look anywhere else
Are you only concentrating on work?
Ah...
[Meaningful music]
As there is only dragon in your life
Even to the successor
That's what you want.
So what did you say?
I answered it as is.
As much as the general manager
No one just works
(In-kyung) If you just do what you said,
I think it will work
I guess so.
(Edited) The head of the department and I
I thought it looked similar
[Juyeon and Sujeong’s laughter]
[Sound of tapping game console]
(Edited) The head of the department
Because he's just my boss.
What about dating or marriage?
I've never thought about it
(Hyoseon) I hope you don’t have to be disappointed.
Like before
For useless things
I wasted my time
Come to your senses, Ban Juyeon
Don't make that mistake twice
Well organized.
[Junsu’s happy exclamation and laughter]
(Edited) That’s it for today
(Junsu) Thank you for your hard work
[Junsu’s sigh]
Doesn’t the team leader come home from work?
Did you stop by the general manager’s office?
(Junsu) Huh?
Ah...
Ah, because of a real blind date.
You're not going to get scolded, right?
I guess it's because of something else.
That's right, it's overkill, that's right
[Mouse operation sound]
(Junsu) Unless you are interested in something from the team leader.
- That's right.
- Right?
yes
Then I'll just go in.
(Junsu) Goodbye
That Junsu!
(Edited) Mr. Junsu
Mr. Junsu
[Laughing] Is there anything I can help you with?
what kind of man
[humorous music]
(Sujeong) Be careful of flirting
If you come to a woman’s house late at night
Why is that so?
I'm interested
Then why do you call yourself a man?
Why are you getting angry because I don’t see it?
100% yes
So what about kissing after drinking?
And forget it
[Glancing sound effect]
You're not talking about the team leader, are you?
[Head shaking sound effect]
Um, no.
I'm talking about comics, comics, romance comics.
(Junsu) Uh...
I read this a while ago
This Namjoo’s psychology
I just can't understand it
(Edited) Is there anything Mr. Junsu?
I wonder if I can understand
[Junsu’s groan of worry]
(Junsu) Do you read comic books too?
Are we opening a pop-up?
What do I do?
(Junsu) Oh, that’s right
Oh, because your hobby is self-improvement.
So, yeah, whatever.
Unless you don't know
(Junsu) But
That's so obvious
That's a cliché, a cliché
[Humorous music-continued]
Did you kiss me?
Did you really forget that?
I'm just pretending I forgot
Why are you pretending you forgot?
I wonder if it's a car
[surprised gasp]
(Junsu) The original male protagonists were
I don't have the courage to confess
That's the rule
[Glancing sound effect]
Please leave work
Okay
(Junsu) Please work hard
[Interesting music]
Somehow
I thought it was strange
I didn't see it that way.
Was it a lack of courage?
[laughter]
[Knocking sound]
(Juyeon) Come in
[light cough]
(Edit) That...
You said you wanted to see me before work.
(Juyeon) Ah
Why?
I'm going on a blind date
Did you call me because you were concerned?
Are you trying to stop me from dating?
no
As Assistant Manager Yang said, Team Leader Baek is dating.
Because I’m not the type of person to work sloppily.
I don't care
(Main role) I am the boss
It's not my part to get involved.
[Embarrassed laughter]
You can just be honest.
[Sound of flipping documents]
How can you be more honest than this?
yes?
Ah, then
Then why did you come to my house?
Are you telling me not to meet Director Kim?
Playboy is really
Because we need to be careful
I gave you attention.
(Juyeon) Anyone would have stopped me
Don’t get me wrong, it’s like love for humanity.
[Sound of flipping documents]
[absurd gasping sound]
Regarding the contract with Strong Ranch, the Chairman
Team Leader Baek praised you a lot.
When negotiating your return salary
There will be good news
Bonuses will also be paid.
I called you to talk about this.
[Sad music]
Aren't you happy?
They say money can make you feel better in 1 second
Haha
I'm happy
[Awkward laughter]
thank you
Go out, then
[Sound of flipping documents]
(Edited) Illusion?
[Humorous sound effects]
Am I the only one who made a mistake?
[Kiss sound effect]
[Interesting music]
[Knocking on door]
The general manager
Are you even going to kiss me out of love for humanity?
- kiss?
- Yes.
You kissed me when you were drunk.
(Edited) Am I still mistaken?
That's not what confused me!
Ah...
I apologize if I did that.
Well, I'm sorry now...
(Juyeon) But
Is that something to be so angry about?
yes?
No way, Baek Soo-jeong
Did you like that kiss?
[surprised gasp]
(Edited) Mr...
[Door lock operating sound]
What's going on?
[Sound of door closing]
(Edited) This
I want to return it
(Juyeon) What is this money?
(Edited) Think of it as a rental fee.
It wasn't what I wanted
And never again
Don't recommend this comic book
Because it's childish and I'm dying
I learn about love by watching things like this.
I'm different from my first love
[humorous music]
Grown adults keep seeing things like this, right?
Then keep kicking
It's just that I'll be dumped forever
I told you to do it so carelessly
It's not a story
I also paid attention
With love for humanity
(Juyeon) Take it
To someone who doesn't even know the value of the work
Because I have no intention of receiving this kind of money.
Baek Soo-jeong, you really need to improve your perspective.
Because I don't have eyes to see that way
Aren’t you even deceived by your first love?
[Door lock operation sound]
[Door lock operating sound]
[Rough breathing]
[light music]
[Heavy breathing]
Kiss?
It was bad
There’s no way it was good just because it wasn’t good!
IC
[sigh]
[Call connection tone]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Sujeong) Sister
Uh, Sujeong-ah
(Edit) That...
I want to go on that blind date
Huh?
Are you going on a blind date?
uh
[surprised gasp]
[Heavy breathing]
[Groans of joy]
(Hajin) Looking at the condition
More than two people
I don't think we'll ever get closer
Sujeong
As a subordinate who curses at his boss
I'm completely back
There's nothing to worry about now
Boy, if I had known it would be like this, I would have stayed quiet.
For no reason, to team leader Baek Soo-jeong.
Looks like I'll only get hate
[Embarrassed laughter]
Anyway, I'm glad
Because we won't get hurt twice
But why did Shin Won start from earlier?
Are you working at the store?
(Hajin) Last time, he followed me to the market.
No, under the pretext of a mock operation.
To help with work and get points?
What do you do by taking points from me?
Have you forgotten what I confessed?
Oh, that
Have you forgotten that I rejected you?
No, there is a saying that says three times.
(Hajin) I thought you had a cool style?
(Shinwon) Me too
I thought so, I
[Slight response]
If you're coming to the store for that reason
I feel a bit burdened, don’t I?
[Calm music]
(Hajin) Was it that good that day?
Well, of course I liked it too.
Well, one more time
I think I can sleep well, right?
But I don’t think three times will work?
Well then, whatever the relationship really is.
It seems like it should work
Because I don't like that
What do you want to do?
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
(Eunhee) Oppa
(Shinwon) Why did you come here?
(Eunhee) Because I can’t contact you
Brother, I was really wrong.
I guess I was crazy that day
My brother is always kind
I know you’re a kind person.
I’m jealous because I like you so much
so so easy
Did you say you wanted to break up?
- (Eunhee) Huh?
- (Shinwon) Eunhee
Dating is about trying to be happy.
I want two to be better than one
But when you met me
You were jealous and anxious.
Did I like seeing you like that?
I won't do that anymore
(Eunhee) Please think again, okay?
[Calm music]
(Shinwon) When you said you liked me
I didn't check twice.
Breaking up is the same
It's not like it wasn't once, right?
And don't come here again like this
Because it’s burdensome
Brother!
That's right
It's not like it wasn't once.
Not like me
[Calm music plays]
(Jihoo) Ah...
I...
[light laughter]
Ah, Mr. Yoon Ji-hoo...
Yes, this is Yoon Ji-hoo.
Is that correct, Sujeong?
yes, that's right
[light breathing]
Uh, please sit down.
(Jihoo) Yes
(Edit) Sorry, I was a little late, right?
(Jihoo) Ah...
Oh, you said you were 3 minutes late?
Thanks to you, I can practice smiling
I was relaxing
[light laughter]
Oh, you haven’t eaten yet, right?
I asked
Here is this lobster pasta
They said it was a recommended menu.
Ah, lobster
[Soft music]
(Juyeon) We also prepared lobster so that each person can eat one.
(Jihoo) Uh, do you hate it?
Or are you allergic?
Oh no, I like it.
Shall we eat this?
Ah, yes
(Jihoo) Hey there
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
(Sujeong) I learn about love by watching things like this
I'm different from my first love
Ah, a grown adult
You keep seeing things like this, right?
Then keep kicking
It's just that I'll be dumped forever
Who goes on blind dates?
Ah, team leader.
Is it real?
I asked if it was real
Why are you curious about that?
Between comrades who had the worst first love
Should I salt it?
braided
[Sound of clinking glasses]
(Edited) In the lounge area you mentioned
How about setting up a stage?
Recruiting an artist that fits your target
To attract new customers
I think it will be helpful
Of course, to existing customers as well
We provide entertainment
Broadcast the performance live on social media
Greater promotional effect
You will be able to enjoy it
[Eye rolling sound effect]
Also for promotion of renewal project
It would be nice to use it
Is it possible to schedule it?
yes you can
[Keyboard operation sound]
[wind blowing sound effect]
[Interesting music]
(Nana)
[Notification sound]
(compliance)
(Juyeon) Do you have any other opinions?
None
Let's finish then
[Junsu’s sigh]
(Nana) Wow...
[Sound of car door closing]
Mr. Soojung!
[Calm music]
[Sound of window rolling down]
(Hyo-seon) Director Ban, what do you do when you’re not riding?
[Sound of car door opening]
[Sound of car door closing]
(Jihoo) They said it might be late
Did you get off work early?
Yes, fortunately
Then
Shall we go?
yes
[Continuous camera shutter sound]
(Host) Next, there will be an appreciation plaque award ceremony.
Who donated the largest amount last year?
This is Ban Ju-yeon, the general manager of Yongseong Department Store.
Losing a family member and needing a helping hand
Thank you for helping children in need
thank you so much
[People applauding]
The following are former foundation scholarship recipients:
Violinist Yuria Yang
There will be a performance
[Violin playing sound]
(President) A busy person
When did you do something so good again?
Anyway, it's cool
[President’s laughter]
Yongseong has no worries.
[Continuous camera shutter sound]
so cool
Because there is a successor.
Isn't it?
Of course, to our Cloud Construction as well
There is this guy though
[Embarrassed laughter]
[President’s laughter]
Who says that?
- (President) Yes?
- (Hyoseon) My successor
This is Director Ban Ju-yeon here.
Who says that?
Oh, of course
(President) Isn’t he your only biological grandson?
This is Yongseong, whom I raised like my own child.
(Hyoseon) Unless there is someone who will raise you as well as me
No one takes it for granted
You can't be a successor
[President’s sigh]
I wouldn't know if it were my dead son
[Meaningful music]
If it's for the company
I sincerely
Professional managers are also considering
[Hyosun’s laughter]
Of course
Our class leader
So far, I'm doing very well.
So soon
I also plan to make my face known to the media.
I also officially announced that he is my grandson.
Oh, I see.
[President’s laughter]
Congratulations
thank you
(Hyoseon) When your face becomes known
You should be more careful about your behavior
Do you understand?
yes
I'll keep that in mind
[laughter]
[Angrily breathing]
(Chorus) ♪ Something new today too ♪
[Continuous camera shutter sound]
♪ The sun is rising ♪
♪ Different from yesterday ♪
♪ The day begins ♪
[The choir continues singing]
(Chaebol man) Your chairman
They say I can drink alcohol?
Ugh, hey, well...
[Laughing] Hey, it's a little scary to stare at it, huh?
why? Are you going to fuck me again?
Ah
Miss, I can't do it.
Your president is still here.
Ah, I was caught making a fuss for no reason.
What if I can’t take over the company?
I spent my whole life pleasing old people.
I lived by begging
Isn't it?
huh?
Hey, still
Ah, it's been a while since I've had intuition
Oh, I really
I had so much fun
Juyeon-ah
Ah, you
Why do I live like such a fool?
I realized it again, again
[nervous music]
You're the fat one
Me?
me?
Why me?
You can't understand the atmosphere
I'm in a really bad mood right now
[Embarrassed groan]
[Juyeon’s exasperated sigh]
[Chaebol man laughs]
[laughter]
[Chaebol man's embarrassed groan]
(Juyeon) What should I do?
If someone climbs on you, step on them.
The one who taught me was our president.
your father told me
Did you see the tail wagging?
If you can't learn even if it's taught right in front of you
[Snoring] What should I do, really?
[sigh]
(Edit) I really like the coffee here.
There is a famous cafe
It's an Italian brand.
It's the only store located here
(Jihoo) I know
Oh, me too sometime
I wanted to try it
Yeah, you said it already.
Oh, it's Sujeong's workplace.
After work, I write.
I don't think I'll want to come back
[Laughing] I don’t like it.
From the customer's perspective
Visiting often is also helpful.
(Edited) To real customers like this
It would be better if you could hear a live evaluation.
[Jihoo takes a breath]
(Jihoo) Ah...
You came here for work, not for a date?
[Embarrassed laughter]
(Sujeong) I heard the desserts there are delicious too.
[Jihoo’s light smile]
Do you like sweets?
(Jihoo) Yes, I like sweet and bitter
Regardless, I eat everything well.
(Edited) Ah...
You both eat well.
(Jihoo) Oh, so much
Does it matter if everyone eats well?
Looks a bit tasteless
Oh no
It's good because it's not too picky.
[Sujeong and Jihoo’s light laughter]
[Jihoo sighs]
It's really delicious
There's a reason it's famous
[Happy laughter]
That's a relief
A good person like Sujeong
why until now
I wonder if you never had a boyfriend.
- Me?
- Yes
[takes a breath]
Have you ever had a lot of snow?
[light laughter]
[Jihoo chuckles]
Ah, well, I could just meet anyone.
I think it would be better alone, it’s comfortable.
(Jihoo) Um
(Edited) Mr. Ji-hoo is really unexpected, isn’t he?
I think you'll be popular
Really?
Actually, I’m someone like Sujeong.
I was waiting
It feels bitter, doesn’t it?
[Jihu’s lament]
It wasn't there because I felt it.
[Ji-hoo and Su-jeong laugh]
Ah, Mr. Sujeong.
Well, if it's okay with you, I'm at the department store.
Can I do some shopping?
I just needed some clothes.
I think Sujeong will make a good choice.
Oh, yes, I like it.
[Exciting rock music sound]
(Singer) ♪ Your reflection in my eyes ♪
♪ Where am I in those empty gazes ♪
♪ You shed tears of blood ♪
♪ Be shattered into shadow's fall ♪
♪ Go away Go away disappear ♪
♪ That smile stained with your lies ♪
♪ There are no second chances ♪
(Juyeon) Maybe this
Enjoying the outside world
my last play
But why
Isn't it fun?
[Calm music]
[Exciting rock music sound]
(Singer) ♪ There is no such thing as a second chance ♪
♪ Go away Go away ♪
(Woman) It’s not really
Oh, what are you saying, really?
What is a man
Does he look like a man now?
[Calm music]
(Edited) Child, what is a man
I heard you’re the same age as Soobin Baek.
Will I look like a man?
It's ridiculous
If you're young, aren't you a man?
[laughter]
[Refreshing elasticity]
Why me?
What's wrong with me?
I have no eyes to see
[absurd gasping sound]
But why
I’m pretty Baek Soo-jeong, right?
[Sound of pouring makgeolli]
[Mysterious sound effect]
(Juyeon) Why do you keep ignoring people?
(Edited) When am I?
(Edited) How about this?
I think it’s neat and fits well.
(Jihoo) Huh? Oh, that's good.
I like it
size
Oh, wait a minute.
yes
(Jihoo) Hey there
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Sujeong’s surprised moan]
[Calm music]
[The door slams shut]
[Sparkling sound effect]
Director
(Edited) No
What if I come here like this?
A person who tries so hard to hide
(Juyeon) So
I know it's crazy too
But why here
I remember everything
That
It was my first kiss
(Clerk) Oh my, why isn’t this opening?
Oh my
Ugh, strange.
[Urgent music]
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
(Edited) Oh, then let's go out on a date?
(Juyeon) I’m not sorry for kissing you
Because that's not a mistake
[Mobile phone closing sound]
I don't even like dating
I really don't like having unique tastes.
(Juyeon) Why do you keep avoiding me?
(Hyoseon) Study?
What's there?
(Juyeon) What I like is
Because it was all a secret
[Knocking sound]
(Edited) Is it inside the headquarters?
(Juyeon) I still have Baek Soo-jeong
I think everything will be okay
I like it